A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Office of the Secretary of Commerce and Trade, 1994-2006 (bulk 2002-2005)
Library of Virginia
- III. Budget and Legislative Files, 2002-2005., Extent: 1.80 cubic feet (4 boxes). (Box 56-59)
  - Subseries III.A. Budget Files, 2002-2005., Extent: 1.35 cubic feet. (Box 56-58)
    This subseries is housed in 3 boxes and is arranged by budget cycle. Subdivisions are: 2002-2004 Biennial Budget and 2004-2006 Biennial Budget Issues. Notable documents include: Agency Contingency Budget Reduction Plans (7, 11, 15%) for Secretary of Commerce and Trade agencies, September-October 2002 (b56, f8-9 and b57, b1); and budget development documents for FY2002-2004 (b57, f2-3). Subseries contains agendas, budget documents, correspondence, memorandums, legislation, presentations, notes, handouts, talking points, e-mail, and reports.
    - 2002-2004 Biennial Budget
      - Budget Documents, 2002-2003 (Box 56, Folder 1)
      - Governor Warner's Proposed Amendments to the 2002-204 Biennial Budget, 20 December 2002 (Box 56, Folder 2)
      - Secretarial Budget, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 3)
      - Commerce and Trade Agency Budget Concerns, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 4)
      - Agency Budget Memos, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 5)
      - Miscellaneous Budget Records, 2002-2004 (part one) (Box 56, Folder 6)
      - Miscellaneous Budget Records, 2002-2004 (part two) (Box 56, Folder 7)
      - Budget Reduction Plans, General, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 8)
      - DPOR Budget Reduction Plan, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 9)
      - VDACS Budget Reducation Plan, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 9)
      - VEDP Budget Reducation Plan, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 9)
      - Tourism Budget Reduction Plan, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 9)
      - Forestry Budget Reduction Plan, 2002 (Box 57, Folder 1)
      - Mines, Minerals and Energy Budget Reduction Plan, 2002 (Box 57, Folder 1)
      - Minority Business Budget Reduction Plan, 2002 (Box 57, Folder 1)
      - DBA Budget Reduction Plan, 2002 (Box 57, Folder 1)
      - Racing Commission Budget Reduction Plan, 2002 (Box 57, Folder 1)
      - DHCD Budget Reduction Plan, 2002 (Box 57, Folder 1)
      - Board of Accountancy Budget Reduction Plan, 2002 (Box 57, Folder 1)
      - Labor and Industry Budget Reduction Plan, 2002 (Box 57, Folder 1)
      - SMC Budget Reduction Plan, 2002 (Box 57, Folder 1)
      - VEC Budget Reduction Plan, 2002 (Box 57, Folder 1)
      - Budget Development for FY2002-2004, 2002 (part one) (Box 57, Folder 2)
      - Budget Development for FY2002-2004, 2002 (part two) (Box 57, Folder 3)
      - Budget Reductions, Executive Offices, 23 October 2002 (Box 57, Folder 4)
      - Budget, Program Cuts, October 2002 (Box 57, Folder 5)
      - Reviews of Commerce and Trade Agency Budget Reductions for FY 2002, FY 2003 and FY 2004 (Box 57, Folder 6)
      - Budget Priorities, 2003 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - 2004-2006 Biennial Budget Issues
      - Budget Issues, 2005 (Box 57, Folder 8)
      - Streamline Sales Tax, 2004 (Box 57, Folder 9)
      - State Agency Budget Concerns, 2004 (Box 57, Folder 10)
      - Tobacco Commission Budget, 2004 (Box 58, Folder 1)
      - Miscellaneous Budget Records, 2003-2004 (part one) (Box 58, Folder 2)
      - Miscellaneous Budget Records, 2003-2004 (part two) (Box 58, Folder 3)
      - 05-06 Budget Program Elimination Proposals, 2003 (Box 58, Folder 4)
      - 05-05 Budget Requests, 2003-2004 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Subseries III.B. Legislative Files, 2002-2005., Extent: 0.45 cubic feet. (Box 58-59)
    This subseries is housed in 2 boxes and is arranged by legislative session. Contains proposed legislation related to Commerce and Trade agencies. Subseries contains agendas, budget documents, correspondence, memorandums, legislation, presentations, notes, talking points, e-mail and reports.
    - 2002-2003 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - SB 554 (2002) (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - 2004 Agency Legislation, 2003 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Governor's Tax Proposal, 2004 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - 2004 Legislative Session (part one) (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - 2004 Legislative Session (part two) (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - 2005 Legislative Proposals, 2004-2005 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - VEC Legislation, 2004-2005 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - 2005 Commerce and Trade Agency Budget, 2004 (Box 59, Folder 6)
- IV. Assigned State Agencies, 1994-2006., Extent: 16.10 cubic feet (20 boxes). (Box 60-79)
  Series is divided into to subgroups: Agency Weekly Reports and Correspondence and Supporting Documentation from Commerce and Trade state agencies. The Agency Weekly Reports are housed in 2 boxes and are arranged alphabetically by agency by agency and chronologically therein. Reports were submitted each week by agency heads from the Board of Accountancy, Dept. of Business Assistance, Dept. of Housing and Community Development, Dept. of Labor and Industry, Dept. of Mines, Minerals and Energy, Dept. of Minority Business Enterprise, Dept. of Professional and Occupational Regulation, State Milk Commission, Virginia Economic Development Partnership, Virginia Employment Commission, Virginia Housing Development Authority, Virginia Racing Commission, Virginia Resources Authority, Virginia Tourism Corporation, and Virginia Tobacco Indemnification and Community Revitalization Commission to the Secretary of Commerce and Trade. The Secretary than used this information to compile his weekly report sent to the Governor and Chief of Staff (see accession 42624). The level of detail varied for each agency. Each report contains information on legislation, items requiring immediate attention of the Governor or Secretary, Governor's initiatives/special projects, agency matters/operations, events/agency visits, audits/investigations/compliance, stakeholder issues and pending decisions.
  The Correspondence and Supporting Documentation from Commerce and Trade state agencies are housed in 16 boxes. Records are from the following agencies: Board of Accountancy, Dept. of Business Assistance, Dept. of Housing and Community Development, Dept. of Labor and Industry, Dept. of Mines, Minerals and Energy, Dept. of Minority Business Enterprise, Dept. of Professional and Occupational Regulation, Virginia Economic Development Partnership, Virginia Employment Commission, Virginia Housing Development Authority, Virginia Racing Commission, Virginia Resources Authority, Virginia Tobacco Indemnification and Community Revitalization Commission and Virginia Tourism Corporation. Notable topics include: Virginia trade missions and Jamestown 2007. Also included in this subgroup are records related to the Small, Women and Minority (SWAM) procurement program initiated by Governor Warner.
  - Agency Weekly Reports
    - Board of Accountancy, 17 April 2002-30 December 2003 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Board of Accountancy, 13 January 2004-4 January 2006 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Dept. of Business Assistance, 23 January 2002-30 December 2003 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Dept. of Business Assistance, 14 January 2004-4 January 2006 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Dept. of Housing and Community Development, 16 January-18 December 2002 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Dept. of Housing and Community Development, 2 January-30 December 2003 (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Dept. of Housing and Community Development, 14 January-29 December 2004 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Dept. of Housing and Community Development, 5 January 2005-4 January 2006 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Dept. of Labor and Industry, 16 July 2002-24 December 2003 (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Dept. of Labor and Industry, 14 January 2004-4 January 2006 (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - Dept. of Mines, Minerals and Energy, 16 January-18 December 2002 (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - Dept. of Mines, Minerals and Energy, 8 January-17 December 2003 (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - Dept. of Mines, Minerals and Energy, 5 January-29 December 2004 (Box 60, Folder 13)
    - Dept. of Mines, Minerals and Energy, 5 January 2005-4 January 2006 (Box 60, Folder 14)
    - Dept. of Minority Business Enterprise, 9 January-18 December 2002 (Box 60, Folder 15)
    - Dept. of Minority Business Enterprise, 2 January-30 December 2003 (Box 60, Folder 16)
    - Dept. of Minority Business Enterprise, 21 January 2004-5 January 2005 (Box 60, Folder 17)
    - Dept. of Minority Business Enterprise, 12 January 2005-4 January 2006 (Box 60, Folder 18)
    - Dept. of Professional and Occupational Regulation, 16 January-18 December 2002 (Box 60, Folder 19)
    - Dept. of Professional and Occupational Regulation, 8 January-30 December 2003 (Box 60, Folder 20)
    - Dept. of Professional and Occupational Regulation, 7 January-29 December 2004 (Box 60, Folder 21)
    - Dept. of Professional and Occupational Regulation, 5 January 2005-4 January 2006 (Box 60, Folder 22)
    - State Milk Commission, 16 January 2002-18 June 2003 (Box 60, Folder 23)
    - Virginia Economic Development Partnership, 16 January-31 December 2002 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Virginia Economic Development Partnership, 8 January-30 December 2003 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Virginia Economic Development Partnership, 14 January-29 December 2004 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Economic Development Partnership, 5 January-29 June 2005 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Virginia Economic Development Partnership, 6 July 2005-4 January 2006 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Virginia Employment Commission, 23 January-18 December 2002 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Virginia Employment Commission, 8 January-30 December 2003 (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Virginia Employment Commission, 21 January-29 December 2004 (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Virginia Employment Commission, 5 January 2005-4 January 2006 (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - Virginia Housing Development Authority, 30 January-18 December 2002 (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - Virginia Housing Development Authority, 8 January-30 December 2003 (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - Virginia Housing Development Authority, 14 January-29 December 2004 (Box 61, Folder 12)
    - Virginia Housing Development Authority, 5 January 2005-4 January 2006 (Box 61, Folder 13)
    - Virginia Racing Commission, 16 January 2002-4 January 2006 (Box 61, Folder 14)
    - Virgninia Resources Authority, 16 January 2002-17 December 2003 (Box 61, Folder 15)
    - Virgninia Resources Authority, 14 January-14 December 2005 (Box 61, Folder 16)
    - Virginia Tourism Corporation, 3 January-23 December 2002 (Box 61, Folder 17)
    - Virginia Tourism Corporation, 3 January-19 December 2003 (Box 61, Folder 18)
    - Virginia Tourism Corporation, 3 January-31 December 2004 (Box 61, Folder 19)
    - Virginia Tourism Corporation, 1 January-30 December 2005 (Box 61, Folder 20)
    - Virginia Tobacco Indemnification and Community Revitalization Commission, 21 January-6 December 2002 (Box 61, Folder 21)
    - Virginia Tobacco Indemnification and Community Revitalization Commission, 13 January-19 December 2003 (Box 61, Folder 22)
    - Virginia Tobacco Indemnification and Community Revitalization Commission, 19 January-30 December 2004 (Box 61, Folder 23)
    - Virginia Tobacco Indemnification and Community Revitalization Commission, 3 January-18 November 2005 (Box 61, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence from State Agencies
    - Board of Accountancy
      - Board of Accountancy, 2001-2005 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Dept. of Business Assistance
      - Bond Approvals, 2002-2005 (Box 64, Folder 1)
      - General Correspondence, 2002 February-December (Box 64, Folder 2)
      - General Correspondence, 2003 January-July (Box 64, Folder 3)
      - General Correspondence, 2003 August-December (Box 64, Folder 4)
      - General Correspondence, 2004 January-August (Box 64, Folder 5)
      - General Correspondence, 2004 September-December (Box 64, Folder 6)
      - General Correspondence, 2005 January-November (Box 64, Folder 7)
      - Manufacturing in Virginia Overview, 2002 (Box 64, Folder 8)
      - Monthly Reports, August 2005 (Box 64, Folder 9)
      - Oklahoma Contingent Tax Credit Model, 2003-2004 (Box 64, Folder 10)
      - Report-JLARC Review of the Virginia Small Business Development Center Program, 2002 (Box 64, Folder 11)
      - Report-Recommendations for First Round of Grant Awards, Virginia Small Business Incubator, 2002-2003 (Box 64, Folder 12)
      - Report-Recommendations for Funding the Small Business Incubator Program, 2002 (Box 64, Folder 13)
      - Report-Recommendations for Funding Virginia Small Buisness Incubator Program, 2003 (Box 64, Folder 14)
      - Report-Recommendations for Second Round Grant Awards, Virginia Small Business Incubator Program, 2004 (Box 64, Folder 15)
      - Report-Virginia Small Business Incubator Program for Senate and House Appropriations Committees, 2002-2004 (Box 64, Folder 16)
      - Small Business Administration, 2002-2004 (Box 64, Folder 17)
      - Virginia Small Business Advisory Board, 2004 (Box 64, Folder 18)
      - Small Business Initiative, 2003-2004 (Box 64, Folder 19)
      - Small Business Initiatives, 2003-2005 (Box 64, Folder 20)
      - Virginia Small Business Financing Authority Annual Report, 2004 (Box 64, Folder 21)
      - Virginia Capital Resource Directory (Box 64, Folder 22)
    - Dept. of Housing and Community Development
      - Affordable Housing Regulatory Barriers, 2000 (Box 65, Folder 23)
      - Appalachian Forward: Four-Year Development Plan for the Appalachian Region of Virginia, 2003 (Box 65, Folder 24)
      - Appalachian Regional Commission, 1998-2002 (Box 65, Folder 25)
      - Appalachian Regional Commission, 2000-2004 (Box 65, Folder 26)
      - Appalachian Regional Commission, 2000 (Box 65, Folder 27)
      - Appalachian Regional Commission, 2001 (Box 65, Folder 28)
      - Appalachian Regional Commission, 2002-2004 (Box 65, Folder 29)
      - Appalachian Regional Commission, 2003 (Box 65, Folder 30)
      - Appalachian Regional Commission, 2004-2005 (Box 65, Folder 31)
      - Appalachian Regional Commission Annual Strategy Statement, 1997-2001 (Box 65, Folder 32)
      - Appalachian Regional Commission Development Plans, 1998 (Box 66, Folder 1)
      - Appalachian Regional Commission Distressed Counties Grant Recommendations, 1998-2000 (Box 66, Folder 2)
      - Appalachian Regional Commission Quorum Meeting, 27 February 2000 (Box 66, Folder 3)
      - Appalachian Regional Commission Special Ballot, 1998-2000 (Box 66, Folder 4)
      - Appalachian Regional Commission, Tobacco Indemnification, 2004 (Box 66, Folder 5)
      - Audit, 1999 (Box 66, Folder 6)
      - Block Grant Program, Local Innovation and Urgent Need Grants, 2002 (Box 66, Folder 7)
      - Community Development Block Grants, 2001-2004 (Box 66, Folder 8)
      - Community Development Block Grants, 2002-2005 (Box 66, Folder 9)
      - Derelict Structures Fund, 1999-2000 (Box 66, Folder 10)
      - Empowerment Zones, 1994-2002 (Box 66, Folder 11)
      - Enterprise Zone Program, 1998-2001 (Box 66, Folder 12)
      - Enterprize Zone Program, 2001-2004 (Box 66, Folder 13)
      - Fire Marshall Program, 1995 (Box 66, Folder 14)
      - Fire Marshall Program, 1995-1998 (Box 66, Folder 15)
      - General Correspondence, 2002 (Box 66, Folder 16)
      - General Correspondence, 2002 (Box 66, Folder 17)
      - General Correspondence, 2002 (Box 66, Folder 18)
      - General Correspondence, 2003 (Box 66, Folder 19)
      - General Correspondence, 2003 (Box 66, Folder 20)
      - General Correspondence, 2004 (Box 66, Folder 21)
      - General Correspondence, 2005 (Box 66, Folder 22)
      - General Correspondence, 2005-2006 (Box 66, Folder 23)
      - Governor's Housing Conference, 1998 (Box 66, Folder 24)
      - Pearlene J. Hamler, 2002-2005 (Box 66, Folder 25)
      - Homeless Intervention Program, 2001-2003 (Box 66, Folder 26)
      - Housing Study Commission, 1994-2001 (Box 66, Folder 27)
      - Industrial Site Development Program Fund, 1998-1999 (Box 67, Folder 1)
      - Industrial Site Development Program Fund, 1999-2000 (Box 67, Folder 2)
      - Ivanhoe Civic League, 1993-1994 (Box 67, Folder 3)
      - Main Street Program, 1994-2004 (Box 67, Folder 4)
      - Manufactured Housing Board, 1998-2000 (Box 67, Folder 5)
      - Planning District Commissions, General Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 67, Folder 6)
      - Planning District Commissions, General Correspondence, 1993-1996 (Box 67, Folder 7)
      - Planning District Commission, General Correspondence, 1994-2004 (Box 67, Folder 8)
      - Proclamations and Certificates, 2004-2005 (Box 67, Folder 9)
      - Regional Competitiveness Act, 1999 (Box 67, Folder 10)
      - Regional Competitiveness Program, 1997-2000 (Box 67, Folder 11)
      - Regional Competitiveness Program, 1997-2005 (Box 67, Folder 12)
      - Regulation Review, 1997-1998 (Box 67, Folder 13)
      - Strategic Plan, 1998-1999 (Box 67, Folder 14)
      - Virginia Enterprise Initiative, 1994-1996 (Box 67, Folder 15)
      - Virginia Housing Partnership Fund, 1997-1999 (Box 67, Folder 16)
      - Virginia Individual Development Accounts, 2000-2003 (Box 67, Folder 17)
      - Vivian Anderson File, 1998-2000 (Box 67, Folder 18)
      - Vivian Anderson File, 1998-2000 (Box 67, Folder 19)
      - Weatherization Program, 1994-1996 (Box 67, Folder 20)
    - Dept. of Labor and Industry
      - Apprenticeship Program, 1998-2001 (Box 65, Folder 8)
      - Certificates of Recognition and Proclaimations, 2004-2005 (Box 65, Folder 9)
      - General Correspondence, 2002 (Box 65, Folder 10)
      - General Correspondence, 2002 (Box 65, Folder 11)
      - General Correspondence, 2003 (Box 65, Folder 12)
      - General Correspondence, 2003 (Box 65, Folder 13)
      - General Correspondence, 2004 (Box 65, Folder 14)
      - General Correspondence, 2004 (Box 65, Folder 15)
      - General Correspondence, 2005 (Box 65, Folder 16)
      - Migrant and Seasonal Farm Workers, 1996-1999 (Box 65, Folder 17)
      - Migrant and Seasonal Farm Workers, 2000-2003 (Box 65, Folder 18)
      - Report-Migrant Worker Policy Committee Annual Reports, 1998-2000 (Box 65, Folder 19)
      - Report-Migrant and Seasonal Farm Workers Biennial Report, 2000 (Box 65, Folder 20)
      - Report-Economic Impact of Migrant, Seasonal, and H-2A Farmworkers on the Virginia Economy, undated (Box 65, Folder 21)
      - Wages Denied, 2003-2004 (Box 65, Folder 22)
    - Dept. of Mines, Minerals and Energy
      - Accident Investigation Report, Surface Coal Mine, 2004 (CD) (Box 64, Folder 23)
      - Accident Investigation Report, Surface Coal Mine, 2004 (Box 64, Folder 24)
      - Air Quality and Energy Policy in Virginia (Box 64, Folder 25)
      - Board of Coal Mining Examiners Profile, 2003 (Box 64, Folder 26)
      - Committee to Study Mine Safety, 2004 (Box 64, Folder 27)
      - Energy Reduction Program, 1992-1993 (Box 64, Folder 28)
      - General Correspondence, 2002 (Box 64, Folder 29)
      - General Correspondence, 2003 (Box 64, Folder 30)
      - General Correspondence, 2004 (Box 64, Folder 31)
      - General Correspondence, 2005-2006 (Box 64, Folder 32)
      - Inman Rockfall Hearing, 2004 (Box 65, Folder 1)
      - Issues of Concern in Dickenson County, undated (Box 65, Folder 2)
      - Mine Tour at Consol Energy's Buchanan No. 1 Mine, Mavidale, Virginia, 10 August 2004 (Box 65, Folder 3)
      - Report-Oklahoma Refinery Report, 2005 (Box 65, Folder 4)
      - Virginia Coal Tax Credit, 1999-2000 (Box 65, Folder 5)
      - Virginia Energy Plan, 1991-1994 (Box 65, Folder 6)
      - Virginia Energy Plan, 1996-2001 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Dept. of Minority Business Enterprise
      - A Proposal to Conduct a Disparity Study, 2003 (Box 62, Folder 9)
      - Virginia Disparity Study-MGT of America, Inc., 2003 (Box 62, Folder 13)
      - Correspondence, 2002-2004 (Box 62, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence, 2004-2005 (Box 62, Folder 11)
      - Governor's Advisory Commission on Minority Business Enterprise, 2002 (Box 62, Folder 12)
      - Governor's Advisory Commission on Minority Business Enterprise, 2002 (Box 62, Folder 18)
      - Providing Access to Capital for Entrepreneurs, 2002 (Box 62, Folder 14)
      - Regulation Certification of Minority Business, 2004 (Box 62, Folder 19)
      - Report of the Governor's Minority Business Enterprise Advisory Commission, September 2003 (Box 62, Folder 16)
      - Report on Audit, 2003-2004 (Box 62, Folder 17)
      - A Study of the Commonwealth of Virginia Minority Certification Program, 2002 (Box 62, Folder 15)
      - Women's Business Enterprise Program, undated (Box 62, Folder 20)
    - Dept. of Professional and Occupational Regulation
      - Board of Professional and Occupational Regulation (Cemeteries) (Box 62, Folder 2)
      - Complaint against Maurice Cox, 2002-2003 (Box 62, Folder 3)
      - Complaints, 2002-2003 (Box 62, Folder 5)
      - Complaints, 2005 (Box 62, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence, 2002 (Box 62, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence, 2003 (Box 62, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence, 2004 (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Virginia Economic Development Partnership
      - Air Freight Legislative Study, 2004 (Box 68, Folder 1)
      - Assumptions and Analysis, 2002-2004 (Box 68, Folder 2)
      - Bond Presentation Power Point Slide, 2003 (Box 68, Folder 3)
      - Board of Directors' Meeting, 2004-2005 (Box 68, Folder 4)
      - Bush Industries, 2003 (Box 68, Folder 5)
      - Centecor, 2003 (Box 68, Folder 6)
      - Cree Project, 2004 (Box 68, Folder 7)
      - CropTech (Giles County), 2002 (Box 68, Folder 8)
      - Draft Column for Virginia Weekly (Gov. Warner), undated (Box 68, Folder 9)
      - Virginia Economic Developers Association Membership Directory, 2005-2006 (Box 68, Folder 10)
      - Virginia Economic Development Incentive Fund, 2003-2004 (Box 68, Folder 11)
      - Economic Development Prospects, undated (Box 68, Folder 12)
      - Economic Development Prospects, Broadband Feasibility Proposal, 2004 (Box 68, Folder 13)
      - Economic Development Prospects, Project Traveller, 2004 (Box 68, Folder 14)
      - Economic Development Prospects, The Blue Ridge Music Center, undated (Box 68, Folder 15)
      - Economic Development Prospects, Virginia Economic Trends, 2004 (Box 68, Folder 16)
      - Economic Development Prospects, Wachovia Securities, 2003 (Box 68, Folder 21)
      - Economic Development Strategic Plan, 2005 (Box 68, Folder 17)
      - Executive Director Candidates, 2005 (Box 68, Folder 18)
      - Executive Director Candidates, 2005 (Box 68, Folder 19)
      - Executive Director Search, 2005 (Box 68, Folder 20)
      - Executive Order, Equal Opportunity in State Procurement, 2002 (Box 68, Folder 22)
      - Forbes, 1998-2003 (Box 68, Folder 23)
      - General Correspondence, 2001 (Box 68, Folder 24)
      - General Correspondence, 2002 January-February (Box 68, Folder 25)
      - General Correspondence, 2002 March-April (Box 68, Folder 26)
      - General Correspondence, 2002 April-May (Box 68, Folder 27)
      - General Correspondence, 2002 June-August (Box 68, Folder 28)
      - General Correspondence, 2002 September-December (Box 68, Folder 29)
      - General Correspondence, 2003 January-March (Box 68, Folder 30)
      - General Correspondence, 2003 April-May (Box 68, Folder 31)
      - General Correspondence, 2003 June-August (Box 68, Folder 32)
      - General Correspondence, 2003 October-December (Box 69, Folder 1)
      - General Correspondence, 2003 December (Box 69, Folder 2)
      - General Correspondence, 2004 January-March (Box 69, Folder 3)
      - General Correspondence, 2004 April-May (Box 69, Folder 4)
      - General Correspondence, 2004 June-July (Box 69, Folder 5)
      - General Correspondence, 2004 August-December (Box 69, Folder 6)
      - General Correspondence, 2005 January-March (Box 69, Folder 7)
      - General Correspondence, 2005 April-May (Box 69, Folder 8)
      - General Correspondence, 2005 June-August (Box 69, Folder 9)
      - General Correspondence, 2005 September-November (Box 69, Folder 10)
      - Guiding Principles, 2003 (Box 69, Folder 11)